A Guide to the Correspondence and Subject Files of the Director of the Virginia Dept. of General Services, 1974-2014
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Correspondence and Subject Files of the Director of the Virginia Dept. of General Services, 1974-2014
The Library of Virginia
32072, 32690, 50089, 50788, 50954, 51588, 51723
25 cu. ft. (25 boxes)
LVA
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Accessions 32072, 32690, and 50089, transferred on 02 May 1984.
Accession 50788 transferred 18 March 2013.
Accession 50788 transferred 11 July 2013.
Accession 51588 transferred 24 June 2015.
Accession 51723 transferred 16 February 2016.
Historical Information
The mission of the Dept. of General Services is to provide supportive services to other state agencies, local political subdivisions as appropriate, in the areas of laboratory services; maintenance, operation and construction of facilities; land management; land and facilities acquisition; disposal and sale of material and supplies; risk management; and other related activities. The Commission on State Governmental Management recommended the creation of the Dept. of General Services to be comprised of the then existing Dept. of Purchases and Supplies, Division of Engineering and Buildings, Division of Consolidated Laboratory Services, Dept. of Property Records and Insurance, and several other state agencies functions which were subsequently determined by appropriate authorities to be left outside of the organization of this department.
In 1976, the General Assembly passed H.B. 1240 which called for the establishment of the position of a director of the department and required the appointee to prepare a plan for the organization of this department with implementing legislation. This was accomplished and the 1977 session of the General Assembly enacted Chapter 672 which created the Dept. of General Services. Consistent with this statute, the department was officially implemented on July 1, 1978. This brought together, under the umbrella of the major department, the Dept. of Purchases and Supply, the Division of Engineering, the Division of Consolidated Laboratory Services, and the Dept. of Property Records and Insurance, now called Office of Risk Management. Also included under the umbrella of the authority of the Dept. of General Services are several boards, appeal boards and review councils which are: Consolidated Laboratory Services Advisory Board; Purchase and Supply Appeal Board; Art and Architectural Review and Council and the State Insurance Advisory Board.
Major activities of the department are to maintain and operate facilities at the seat of government; assist in the administration of the capital outlay budget of the Commonwealth; to assist in acquisition of real property either by lease or purchase; to perform centralized purchasing functions of the Commonwealth; to dispose of surplus real property and material and supplies; to provide a comprehensive risk management insurance program for all agencies and institutions; to operate a centralized purchasing and warehousing function for supplying State agencies and certain political subdivisions with equipment and supplies; to acquire or provide printing services for State agencies and institutions; provide central mail and messenger service for State agencies in the area of the seat of government; provide laboratory research and scientific services in the area of environmental sciences; forensic science, microbiology, and product regulation; to provide training to law enforcement personnel in the collection and preservation of evidence; and to conduct programs on inspection and certification of certain laboratories through the state.
Scope and Content
Includes correspondence and subject files that document the planning, direction, and implementation of agency programs and are evidence of actions and policy decisions.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I. Correspondence and Subject Files
Contents List
- Series I. Correspondence and Subject Files, 1974-2007., Extent: 23 cu. ft. (23 boxes).
  - Accession 32072, 1974-1980.
    This accession is arranged in chronological order.
    - Administration and Finance Agency Heads' Meeting, 1977. (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - A./E. Services, n.d.. (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Alexandria, n.d.. (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - APCO Information--J.S.B., 1978. (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Architectural Barriers--American National Standard Specifications, 1977. (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Architectural Barriers--Questionnaires, 1977. (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Architectural and Engineering Firms, 1979. (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Arkansas, 1976. (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Attachment O, 1979. (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Attorney General's Procurement Study, n.d.. (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Bonding Requirements, 1979. (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - California, 1976. (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Capital Outlay, 1980-1982. (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Capitol Outlay #1, 1979. (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Capital Outlay--Budget Preparation Calendar, 1980-1982. (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Capital Outlay Budget, 1974-1976. (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Central Garage Motor Pool, 1977. (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Change Orders, n.d.. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - C. O. Progress Report, September 30, 1981. (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Commission on State Governmental Management--Reports, 1975. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Committee for Negotiations with VEPCO and APCO, 1974. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Commonwealth Intern Program, 1979. (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Consolidated Laboratory Services, 1976. (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Consolidated Laboratory Services, 1979. (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Consolidated Laboratory Services, 1980. (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Construction, 1979. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Consultant Inventory Forms (JLARC), 1980. (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Contingent Fees, 1980. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Contract with Appalachian Power Company, December 31, 1974. (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Contract with Virginia Electric and Power Company, December 18, 1974. (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Council of State Governments, 1978. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Criteria and Procedures--Drinking Water Laboratories, 1978. (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - "Davis-Bacon" Acts, n.d.. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - DCLS Board, 1978. (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Dept. of Purchases and Supply--1 of 2, 1978. (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Determination of Goals and Policies for Administration and Finance, 1978. (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - DGS--Organization, 1978. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Division of Consolidated Laboratory Services--for Science, 1979. (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - E and B, 1978. (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - E and B, 1979. (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - E and B--Asbestos Materials in State Buildings, 1979. (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - E and B--Building and Grounds, 1980. (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - E and B--Capital Outlay, 1980. (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - E and B--Capital Oulay Manual, 1980. (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - E and B--General Assembly Building, 1979. (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - E and B--George Mason Law Building, 1980. (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - E and B--Land Management, 1980. (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - E and B--Land Management, 1980. (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - E and B--Leases, 1979. (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - E and B--Maintenance Standards Proposal (MASD), 1980. (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - E and B--Master Site Plan Capitol Square, 1980. (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - E and B--Parking, 1979. (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - E and B--Space Renovations, 1978. (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - E and B--Staff Meetings, 1976. (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - E and B Energy--Coal Conversion/Funding, 1980. (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - E and B Energy--Heating Systems--2 of 3, 1980. (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Econometric Model, Task Force, 1978. (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Electric Cost Estimate Extra Forms, January 17, 1975. (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Energy--Heating Systems, 1979. (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Energy Seminar, May 20, 1978. (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Errors in Bids, n.d.. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - E and B--G. S. Directive #1 Space Request, 1978. (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Escheating, 1980. (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Ethics Provisions, n.d.. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Executive Communications Exchange, 1980. (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Exemptions, n.d.. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Federal Design Assembly, 1978. (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Federal Grants, n.d.. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Federal Regional Council Meeting, December 17, 1978. (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Florida, 1976. (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Fredericksburg, n.d.. (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Functional Summary Forms, 1976. (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Functional Summary Sheets, 1976. (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - GAO Procurement Study, 1978. (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - General Assembly Building HVAC Study, 1980. (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - General Services--Committee, 1977. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Georgia, 1976. (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Goals and Objectives, 1979-1980. (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Goals and Objectives, September 30, 1980. (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Henrico, n.d.. (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - "Highways"--Procurement Legislation, 1981. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - HJR 275--Selection of Architects and Engineers--Washington Committee, 1979. (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Hopkins Commission Reports, 1973. (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - House Document 16, 1957. (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Illinois, 1975. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Inflation--President Carter's Memo to Governor Dalton, November 21, 1978. (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Insurance, 1980. (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Insurance Procurement, n.d.. (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Iowa, 1976. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Issues for 1980's, 1980. (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Issues Sent to Secretary Rowe, 1976. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - JLARC Report--"Capital Outlays in Virginia", 1978. (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - JLARC Report--"Capitol Outlays in Virginia"--2 of 2, 1974. (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Joint Virginia Municipal League-Virginia Association of Counties Steering Committee--VEPCO, 1976. (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Judicial Review, n.d.. (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Kentucky, 1976. (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Leases, 1978. (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Legislation, 1977. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Legislation, 1980. (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Legislative Veto, 1980. (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Local Government Procurement, n.d.. (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Management Review Summary, June 30, 1979. (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Management Review Summary, March 31, 1981. (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Management Review Summary, June 30, 1981. (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Management Review Summary, December 31, 1981. (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Management Review Summary Quarterly Report, June 30, 1980. (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Maryland, 1971. (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Meeting, June 26, 1979. (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Meeting, September 17, 1979. (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Meeting, October 22, 1979. (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Meeting, November 26, 1979. (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Meeting, January 28, 1980. (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Meeting, February 25, 1980. (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Meeting, March 26, 1980. (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Meeting, April 21, 1980. (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Meeting, May 19, 1980. (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Meeting, June 30, 1980. (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Meeting, July 21, 1980. (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Meeting, August 11, 1980. (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Meeting, August 25, 1980. (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Meeting (Public Hearing), August 22, 1979. (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Minnesota, 1975. (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Miscellaneous, 1980. (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous--Electric Consumption and Rate Survey, July 14, 1971. (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Miscellaneous Paperwork, 1974. (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - MPC--General, 1979. (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - MPC--Local Application, 1979. (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - MPC--Other States, n.d.. (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Negotiations with Appalachian Power Company, 1974. (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Negotiations with Appalachian Power Company, 1978. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Negotiations with Appalachian Power Company #2, 1978. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Negotiations with Low Bidder, n.d.. (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Negotiations with Virginia Electric and Power Company--File 1, 1974. (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Negotiations with Virginia Electric and Power Company--File 2, 1974. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Negotiations with Virginia Electric and Power Company--File 3, 1974. (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Newport News, n.d.. (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1980. (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Norfolk, n.d.. (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - North Carolina, 1976. (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Notes on Meetings of Committee for Negotiations with VEPCO and APCO, 1974. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Objectives, 1978-1979. (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Original of Architectural Barriers Report, 1977. (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Original of Legislation Attached to Report, 1976. (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Pennsylvania, 1975. (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Post Employment Restrictions, n.d.. (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Printing and Graphics, 1979. (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Procurement Methods, n.d.. (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Procurement Study #4, 1981. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Procurement Study #5, 1981. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Procurement Study Report, 1981. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Procurement Systems, n.d.. (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Proposed Legislation, 1979. (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Proposed Organization Chart, 1976. (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Proprietory Information, n.d.. (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - P and S--Memos and Directives, 1974-1979. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - P and S Procurement Study #2, 1979. (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - P and S Procurement Study #3, 1980. (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - P and S Procurement Study--Subcommittee SJR 148, 1980. (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - P and S Public Hearing--SJR 14, August 22, 1979. (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Public Cabinet Meetings, 1979. (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Public Hearing (Richmond), June 9, 1980. (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Public Hearing (Roanoke), June 11, 1980. (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Quarterly Progress Report, December 31, 1978. (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Quarterly Progress Report, March 31, 1979. (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Quarterly Progress Report, June 30, 1983. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Quarterly Report, October 16, 1978. (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Quarterly Report, September 30, 1979. (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Quarterly Report, December 31, 1979. (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Quarterly Report, December 31, 1980. (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Quarterly Report, September 30, 1981. (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Quarterly Report, September 30, 1982. (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Quarterly Report, December 31, 1982. (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Quarterly Report, March 31, 1983. (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Quarterly Report Management Review Summary, March 31, 1980. (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Remedies, 1980. (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Roanoke, n.d.. (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Secretary of the Commonwealth, 1976. (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Separate Policy Office, n.d.. (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Services, 1977. (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - SJR 148, n.d.. (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Socioeconomic Policies, 1980. (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - South Carolina, 1976. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Special Committee to Study the Relationship between Electric Companies and Governmental Entities in Virginia #1, 1975. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Special Committee to Study the Relationship between Electric Companies and Governmental Entities in Virginia #2, 1975. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Special Committee to Study the Relationship between Electric Companies and Governmental Entities in Virginia #3, 1975. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Special Committee to Study the Relationship between Electric Companies and Governmental Entities in Virginia #4, 1975. (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Staff Meetings, 1976. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - State Library, 1976. (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Staunton, n.d.. (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Study--Administration, 1979. (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Study--Correspondence, 1980. (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Study--Establishment, 1979. (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Study on House Bill 1240, 1976-1977. (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Summary of Capital Outlay Requests, 1980-1982. (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Support Services--Mrs. Bridgers' Questions, n.d.. (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Task Force on Architectural Barriers--Comparison of Handicap Standards, 1977. (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Task Force on Architectural Barriers--Letters to Agencies, 1977. (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Task Force on Architectural Barriers in State Facilities, 1977. (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Task Force on Architectural Barriers in State Facilities, 1977. (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Task Force on Architectural Barriers in State Facilities #2, 1977. (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Tennessee, 1976. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Toxic Substances Information, 1999. (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Treatises, n.d.. (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Venue, n.d.. (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - VEPCO Contract--3 of 3, 1976. (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - VEPCO Negotiations #1, 1978. (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - VEPCO Negotiations #2, 1978. (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - VEPCO Negotiations #3, 1978. (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - VEPCO Rate Negotiations--1 of 3, 1976. (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - VEPCO Rate Negotiations--2 of 3, 1976. (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - VEPCO Rates, 1976. (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - VEPCO Revenues, Schedules and Recommendations, 1974-1976. (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Virginia Design Assembly, 1978. (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Electric and Power Company, 1972. (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Virginia Electric and Power Company Electric Power Supply, 1972. (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Virginia Procurement Law Study Interim Report to the General Assembly of Virginia, 1980. (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Virginia Public Telecommunications Council, 1978. (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Westinghouse Breach of VEPCO Fuel Supply Contract, 1975. (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Wisconsin, 1971-1976. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Work Papers, 1970. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Accession 32690, 1977-1982.
    - Acquisition of Land, 1981. (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Appalachian Power Company Negotiations, 1980. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Architectural and Engineering Firms, 1980. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Backlog--DCLS, 1981. (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Blanket Bond Program, 1982. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Breathalyzer Tests, 1983. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Budget Amendments, 1981. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Buildings and Grounds, 1982. (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Bureau of Environmental Science #2, 1981-1982. (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Bureau of Forensic Science, 1980. (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Bureau of Forensic Science #3, 1981. (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Bureau of Microbiological Science #2, 1982. (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Capital Outlay, 1982. (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Capital Outlay Requests, 1981. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Christmas, 1978. (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Confederate Memorial Chapel, 1981. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Consolidated Laboratory Services #3, 1981. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Consolidated Laboratory Services Operational Board, 1981. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Consultant and Professional Services, 1980. (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Contaminated Products, 1982. (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - DCLS, 1982. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - DCLS--Building Addition/Renovation, 1982. (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - DCLS--Bureau of Environmental Science, 1981. (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - DCLS--Bureau of Microbiological Science, 1981. (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - DCLS--Forensic Science, 1979. (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - DCLS--Forensic Science Academic Funding, 1982. (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - DCLS--Forensic Science Subcommittee, 1979. (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - DCLS--Gasoline Laboratory, 1981. (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - DCLS--Laboratory Services Advisory Board, 1982. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - DCLS--Northern Virginia Regional Laboratory, 1981. (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - DCLS--Quality Control, 1981. (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - DCLS--Training, 1979. (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Delegation of Authority, 1979. (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Demolition--Saunders Building, 1982. (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Department of Computer Services, 1982. (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Dept. of Corrections House Appropriations Committee, August 1979. (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - DGS Capital Outlay, 1982-1984. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - E and B, January-December 1980. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - E and B #3, 1981. (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - E and B Architect/Engineer Selection--H.B. 601, 1980. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - E and B Building Survey and Recommendation, 1981. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - E and B Buildings and Grounds, 1981. (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - E and B Capital Outlay, 1981. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - E and B Capital Outlay Manual #2, 1980. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - E and B Capital Square, 1981. (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - E and B Central Heating Plant--Capital Square, 1980. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - E and B Construction Management, 1980. (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - E and B Demolition, 1982. (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - E and B Design Build #1, 1980. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - E and B Design Build #2, 1981. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - E and B Disqualification of Contractors, 1980. (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - E and B--Energy, 1979. (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - E and B Energy--Coal Conversion, 1981. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - E and B Energy--Heating Systems, 1980. (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - E and B Federal Reserve Building, 1981. (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - E and B Fire Safety Regulations, 1981. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - E and B Fixed Assets Information System, 1981. (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - E and B General Assembly Building #2, 1981. (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - E and B Handicapped Accessibility, 1979. (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - E and B HJR 83--Study for Hospital in S.W., 1980. (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - E and B Land Management #3, 1981. (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - E and B Leases, 1980. (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - E and B Old Memorial Hospital, 1982. (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - E and B Parking, 1980. (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - E and B Parking, 1982. (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - E and B Payments to General Contractors, 1981. (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - E and B Pre-Cast Concrete Wall Construction, 1979. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - E and B Pre-Planning, 1980. (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - E and B Renovations, 1980. (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - E and B Rental Charges, 1980. (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - E and B Rental Charges, July 17, 1981. (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - E and B Roofing Policies, etc., 1981. (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - E and B Roofing Seminar, 1981. (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - E and B Security, 1981. (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - E and B Space #2, 1981. (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - E and B Space--Old State Office Building, 1980. (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - E and B Statues, State-Owned, Repairing, 1981. (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - E and B Steam Rates (VCU), 1981. (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - E and B Temporary Mobile Buildings, 1980. (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - E and B Virginia State College Central Heating Plant, 1981. (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Emergency and Energy Services, 1981. (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Energy, 1979. (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Energy #2, 1981. (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Engineering and Building Water Conservation, 1980. (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Environmental Science, 1983. (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Executive Compensation Study and Salaries, 1981. (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Finance Building, 1982. (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Fixed Assets #1, 1980. (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Forensic Science, 1982. (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - General Services Insurance Coverage, 1981. (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Governor's Policy--Overtime and Capital Outlay, November 1981. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Green Springs, 1981. (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Handicapped Accessibility #2, 1981. (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Hazardous Wastes, 1982. (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - HDH Procurement Law Papers, 1982. (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Identification Cards Committee, 1981. (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Institutions of Higher Education Request for Exemption Liaison, 1982. (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Insurance Board #1, 1980. (Box 6, Folder 6)